Sorry, sorry...
ごめんごめん...
I never caught a taxi...
タクシー全然捕まんなくてさ...
It took so long...
すげえ時間かかっちゃった...
It's crowded...
混んでるし...
I really dashed...
めっちゃダッシュした...
Because just now... you know...
だってさっきは...ほら...
I sent you a stamp that shows you running really fast...
スタンプだってめっちゃ走ってるやつ送ったじゃん...
I had time to send stamps...
スタンプ送る余裕あった...
I ran super...I sent it while running...
超走った...走りながら送った...
It's cold so I'll go early...
寒いから早く行く...
No, I took it...
いや、取った...
I've already taken it...
もう取ってる取ってる...
It's still cold...
まだ寒いよ...
I'll warm it up...
温めるから...
It heats up quickly...
早く温めるから...
It's cold because it's bare legs, right?
それは生足だから寒いよね、そりゃね...
As always, it's more about style...
相 変わらずスタイルよりは...
I wonder if you were really in a hurry...
本当に急いでたか怪しいんだけど...
No, I was really in a hurry...
いや、めっちゃ急いだよ...
Really... just...
め っちゃ...ちょうど...
Are you busy lately?
最近忙しいの?
recently...
最近...
I'm seriously bored...
マジで暇...
free time?
暇?
If only there was some kind of bonus...
なんかボーナス出てたらもう...
Looks like he's coming to visit soon...
そろそろ遊びに来そうなの...
I seriously don't have any money...
マジでお金ない...
Ah, that's right...
あ、そうなんだよ...
I don't mind if you don't mind...
よかったら合わんし...
Isn't it a bit terrible?
ちょっとひどくないっすか?
Isn't it bad?
ひどくないっすか?
It's true that after a long time of contacting each other, I saw it quickly and decided.
確かになんか連絡久々にしたら 速攻で見て決まったもんだよ
...
Yeah...I'm not going...
うん...行かないのよ...
Hide...
ひでぇ...
I'm seriously bored...
マジで暇よ...
lie...
嘘...
Wouldn't you play if you didn't have money?
お金なかったら遊ばないっすか?
He won't play with me even if I don't have him...
なくてもなんか遊んでくれたりとかはしない...
Eh...
えぇ...
I might think about it once...
一旦考えるかも...
picture?
え?
After all, it's totally fun to go shopping or something like that...
だって普通に買い物とか行ったりとかすんのは全然楽しい...
After all, it's money...
結局金か...
Please let me fall in love with you...
かわいし恋を取らせて...
Because I'm going to bump into you...
ぶつゆくわるから...
Bumping around?
ぶつゆくわる?
Dizzy...
ぼちぼち...
It's like, even though I'm really good at it, it's like when I'm having sex.
なんかさ、めっちゃ食える系なのに なんかエッチの時なんか
...
It's really nice to change your voice a little...
ちょっと 声が変わるのはめっちゃいい...
Safely...
無事...
Awesome...
すげぇ...
Huh?
あれ?
You won't say it directly, right?
直接言わんでしょ?
what?
何?
You won't say that, will you?
それ言わないでしょ?
Do you say it?
言うの?
I'm not angry...
怒ってはないよ...
It's always like this...
普段からもこんな感じで...
cold...
寒い...
I want to be warm...
温まりたい...
chilly?
肌寒い?
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it true that you have good taste in choosing each one?
本当さ、一個一個選ぶやつセンスいい?
What?
何が?
Something black...
なんかブラック...
real?
ほんと?
There are quite a few bras...
結構ブラは...
I tend to choose bus style...
バステリ系選びがち...
Do you tend to choose?
選びがち?
It's still cold...
まだ寒いな...
cold
寒い
...
Is your face okay?
顔 大丈夫かな?
Check it out
チェックして
...
Uru
う る
Sai...
さい...
a...
あ...
cold
寒 い
...
cold...
寒 い...
Oh, it's so bad...
あ、やばいやばい...
cold...
寒い...
it hurts...
痛 い...
I can't help but leave
ついついって離れないね
...
Oh, it's so bad...
あ、 やばいやばい...
you
君
...
go...
いく...
Ah, let's go...
あ、いく...
It's really tight...
めっちゃ締めてる...
No...
いけない...
I can't go...
い けない...
How tight is it?
どんだけ締めてる?
The tightening is amazing...
締めすごい...
I didn't want to let this go...
これ離したくなかった...
Have you been keeping it in?
ずっと入れてる?
Can I let go?
離していい?
Yeah...
うん...
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'm getting rid of a cold...
風邪を落としてるし...
hot
熱い
...
I raised my leg like that
そんな に足を上げちゃって
...
Do you want to enter?
入 れたい?
Then can I enter?
じゃあ入れる?
Hey...
ねえ...
Looks cold...
寒そう...
Haven't you cut it?
切ってない?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
You've peed yourself...
おもらしきたでしょ...
Cool...
クール系の...
Isn't it likely to leak again?
また漏れそうじゃない?
I don't know...
わかんない...
I come out when I'm tired...
僕疲れると出ちゃう...
I'm going to pee
おもらしちゃう
...
It's really tight...
め っちゃ締めてる...
Feels good...
気持ちいい...
terrible...
やばい...
go...
いく...
It's noisy...
うるさいな...
Take it out...
出して...
amazing...
すごい...
So...
めっちゃ...
The same goes for the toy from earlier...
さっきのおもちゃもそうだけどさ...
You'll really tighten up after you go...
行った後でめっちゃ締めるでしょ...
I can't cry...
泣けないんですけど...
It was the first time I saw you peeing today...
今日おもらしたの初めて見た...
I'm sure...it must be today...
確かに...今日なんだろう...
I wish I could do more...
もっといっぱいしちゃえばいい...
It's embarrassing...
恥ずかしいな...
But please come with me and show me a lot of embarrassing girls like that.
でも一緒にちょっとそういう恥ずかしいな子いっぱい見せてよ
...
Seriously?
マ ジ?
Hurry...isn't it early?
早...早くない?
It's always like that...
いつもそうだよね...
You're always early...
いつも早いよね...
revival...
復活...
I keep collecting it in front of you...
あんまの前でずっと溜めてるの...
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I don't think it's a character...
キャラじゃないと思うんだけどさ...
I brought some things that I think would definitely suit me...
絶対似合いそうなやつちょっと持ってきたんだけど...
What?
え、なに?
What kind of thing is it?
どんなやつ?
Fluffy...
ふわふわ...
Lion...fluffy...
リオン...ふわふわ...
Oh no...
やば...
It definitely doesn't suit me...
絶対似合わないよ...
Something like this...
こんなの...
Eh, what is this?
え、なにこれ?
rabbit?
ウサギ?
rabbit
ウサ
Gi...
ギ...
It suits you so well...
似合うじゃん、めっちゃ...
ignore?
無視?
It's so cute...look...
可愛いよめっちゃ...ほら...
Okay...
いいから...
It may not be the character, but it suits her...
キャラじゃないかもしれないけど似合うって...
It's not a character...
キャラじゃないね...
It's not a character, but... you know...
キャラじゃないけど...ほら...
Someone who isn't a character...
キャラじゃないやつをさ...
Oh, no...
え、やば...
You look like a real girl...
めっちゃ女の子って感じでしょ...
Are you going to cut this?
これ切るの?
Is there a gap...
ギ ャップあるのかさ...
Do you like this too?
これも好きなの?
picture?
え?
I mean, I like it...
好きっていうか...
I would like to dress a cool child in something like this...
クール系な子にこういうのをあえて着せてみたい...
Kusenkyuu?
クセンキュー?
Ah, maybe I can go...here too...
あ、いけるかも...こっちも...
That's terrible...
やばいね...
I've never worn anything like this...
こんなの着たことない...
Hey, wear this next time you go to an event...
ちょっとさ、今度イベントの時これ着てきてよ...
event?
イ ベント?
Yeah...
うん...
Ah...this...
あー ...これ...
Are you going to take it home?
持って帰るの?
no...
いや...
It doesn't match my nails though...
爪と合ってないけど...
this is?
これは?
Tie?
結ぶ?
Yeah...
うん...
Eh, I don't think it really suits me...
え、マジで似合ってない気がするんだけど...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Not a character...
キャラじゃない...
So good...
めっちゃいい...
cute...
可愛い...
Looks good on you...
似合う...
It doesn't seem to suit me...
似合わなそうだけど...
It suits you so well...
めっちゃ似合ってる...
I'm wearing this one too and there are 4...
こっちも着て4つも...
This is so fluffy
ふわふわだね、これ
...
Look at this too...
こ っちも見て...
Although it's not a character...
キャラじゃないけど...
Okay, this...
いいな、これ...
So cute...
すげー可愛い...
TRUE?
本当?
You stand up quickly...
立つの早いって...
early...
早い...
Because when I smell it while I'm sleeping, it's amazing.
だって寝てる間から匂い嗅いでたらすげー立つの
...
I don't want to see it myself, but...
自 分で見るのは嫌なんだけど...はず...
Let's buy something for the next event...
今度のイベントの時に何か購入しよう...
Eh, can I go?
え、いけるかな?
Because I'm ready...
準備できてるから...
For some reason...
なんだかんだに...
Can I put it in yet?
もう入れる?
put in?
入れる?
I want to keep it in...
ずっと入れたい...
I can't help it
仕方ないの
...
Feelings together
気 持ちいっしょに
...
Yeah...
うん...
Try holding my hand like this
もうこうやって手を持ってみて
...
Yeah...
うん...
I'm jumpy...
ビクビクしてる...
Sleep again...
また寝る...
It's new so it's stained...
新しいから染みられてる...
It's embarrassing...
恥ずかしいわ...
So cute...
す げー可愛い...
Should...
はず...
Just a little...
ちょっとなんかさ...
It looks like black, but it looks like it would go well with a fluffy white coat.
黒のイメージだけど、白のふわふわコートとかに合いそう
Isn't it?
じゃない?
Coat?
コ ート?
Let's go buy a coat...
コート買いに行こう...
Does it go well with white?
白に合うか?
Let's go...
行こうよ...
Buy it...
買って...
Buy...
買 って ...